# KIASILUA LUBUAKU Arthobelly

Kinshasa on April 21, 1994 (28 years Congolese nationality

Civil **Electronic Engineer** (Admitted thesis) from the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering the POLYTECHNIC Faculty of University of Kinshasa.

Researcher and Designer of private cellular networks based on Software Defined Radio & Opensource Project.

Fellow the Google Africa of Developer Scholarship program and Student in **Associate** Cloud **Engineer** 

#### **SKILLS**

- ✓ Programming and DBMS (C#, JAVA, Python, MATLAB, SQL, Verilog, MySQL)
- ✓ Electronic design and programming of microcontrollers (Eagle, Proteus ISIS, Logisim, FPGA)
- √ System and Network Administration (LINUX, Windows Server Wireshark, Cain and Abel, Cisco Packet Tracer)
- ✓ Office automation (Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- ✓ DevOps Tools (Git)
- ✓ Virtualization technologies (PROXMOX, VirtualBox, Hyper-V and Docker)
- ✓ Project Management (MS Project)
- ✓ Design of telecommunications systems based on SDR (OpenBTS, srsLTE, Open5qs)

#### **LANGUAGES**

- ✓ French
- ✓ English
- ✓ Lingala

#### **POINTS OF INTEREST**

- ✓ Classical Music
- ✓ Drama



- +243819949647 / 844251314
- kiasiluarthobelly@gmail.com
  - Kinshasa, DRC

#### **TRAINING**

University of Kinshasa | 2020 -2021 Admitted to thesis at the Faculty POLYTECHNIQUE - Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering - Electronics Orientation

University of Kinshasa | 2017-2018 Graduated in Applied Sciences at the Faculty POLYTECHNIQUE - Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (TFC Subject: Study and Securing of VoIP technology)

Industrial Technical Institute of GOMBE | 2012-2013

State Diploma in Industrial Electronics

Openclassroom | July 2022 Certificate in Deployment Optimization with Docker

#### **EXPERIENCES**

### DATACENTER POLYTECHNIC FACULTY |

Administrator August 2021- to date

In charge of the administration of the DATACENTER of the POLYTECHNIC Faculty of the University of Kinshasa (LAN & Wi-Fi networks, Servers, Cameras, VoIP...) (Ref :0814443252)

#### **RSAT | Agent marker and Technician**

October 2015-April 2016

Responsible for the installation and sales of equipment for the reception of satellite television (Ref: +243898489987)

## **Electrical and Computer Engineering Club** |

**Member** | 2019-2020

Member of the electronic group of the project DRONE and ROBOT CAR